

MAIA STONE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

INFO

303.909.5353

maiadov@gmail.com

Github @maiastone

LinkedIn @maiastone

Twitter @maiadov

I dig deep into the details and apply technical skills to solve problems. With solid comprehension of the big picture, I can setup a code base, and create smooth digital experiences for intentional user groups. As an entrepreneur with a corporate background, I'm experienced in making strategic and operational decisions, and have had the pleasure of working with and leading highly functional teams.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

iQuery

React

Redux

Ember

TOOLS &

WORKFLOW

Webpack

Github

Sketch

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Turing School of Software and Design

2016 - Present

EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR, FOUNDER

MindSpark, Inc.

2011 - Present

- Developed 38 programs to serve over 1,000 youth, in six schools and four libraries, over five years
- Engage and energize volunteers, board members, event committees, alumni, partnering organizations, and funders

BOOKKEEPER. OFFICE MANAGER

MSW Financial Partners

2008 - Present

- Maintain QuickBooks and financial statements for rental properties, commission income and expenses
- Manage FINRA and SEC compliance

FEATURED WORK

BUDGET APP

A budgeting app for kids allows for easy input of monthly budgeted expenses.

REACT, FIREBASE, WEBPACK, ENZYME

2DO LIST

A responsive and accessible, single page ToDo List.

JQUERY, WEBPACK, SASS, SELENIUM

WEATHER TRACKER

Allows the user to see forecast information for a up to 3 pinned cities.

REDUX, REACT, ENZYME, JEST



MAIA STONE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

INFO

303.909.5353
maiadov@gmail.com
Github @maiastone
LinkedIn @maiastone
Twitter @maiadov

EDUCATION

MASTER OF TAXATION, UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

MBA - REAL ESTATE, UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

BA - PHOTOGRAPHY, UNIVERSITY OF NEW MEXICO

CERTIFICATION

CPA

SKILLS

TDD

Enzyme

Jest

Selenium

DATABASES

Firebase

OTHER

Pair Programming
Agile Development

EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

TAX ANALYST & CONSULTANT

Great-West Life & Annuity Insurance Company

 Preparation of quarterly tax provisions, tax basis balance sheets, deferred tax roll-forward, current tax payable account validation, and annual returns.

Deloitte Tax LLP

• Preparation of tax returns for individuals, trusts, gift and estate tax returns, partnerships, and foundations.

HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT, CATERING & EVENT PLANNING

 Il progressive years in hospitality highlighted by experience with Disney World, Hyatt, and Marriott

VOLUNTEER

Over 10 years of volunteer service on boards, grant making teams, eventplanning teams, and fundraising committees.

EVENT PRODUCTION

Denver Startup Week, Basecamp

2014

Basecamp was host to 6,000 attendees, 40 separate events

STEMosphere, Share Fair

2013

An educational and professional developement exhibition with 5,000 attendees, 40 hands-on exhibitors